var title = 'Traduza para grego.<br>Para substantivos, inclua o artigo definido (ο, η, το...).';

var questions = [

 {
   prompt: "o papai",
   answer: ["ο μπαμπάς", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "a menina",
   answer: ["το κορίτσι", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "a criança",
   answer: ["το παιδί", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "a mulher, esposa",
   answer: ["η γυναίκα", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "o alemão (pessoa)",
   answer: ["ο Γερμανός", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "a senhorita",
   answer: ["η δεσποινίς", "η δεσποινίδα", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "o(a) empregado(a)",
   answer: ["ο ηπάλληλος", "η ηπάλληλος", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "o carregador (de malas)",
   answer: ["ο αχθοφόρος", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "o André",
   answer: ["ο Ανδρέας", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "o Pandelis",
   answer: ["ο Παντελής", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

];